&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：让我们看看+运算符和
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So let's take a look at the spec for the ++ operator and
在本例中，是后缀运算符，因为这是有问题的运算符。
in this case, the postfix operator, since that's the one in question.
您会注意到它是写出来的，并且大多数规范都是这样的。
You'll notice that it is written out, and most of the spec is this way.
它是以某种编号的算法格式写出的。
It is written out in the sorta numbered algorithmic format.
好消息是您是开发人员，开发人员阅读并
The good news is you're developers, and developers read and
整天写算法。
write algorithms all day long.
所以虽然确实有一些具有挑战性的部分需要跳入
So while there are certainly some challenging parts to jumping into
规格，我不想忽略规格是即时的，
the spec, and I don't wanna wash over that the spec is just immediate,
很容易阅读。
it's easy reading.
这绝对是需要努力的。
That definitely takes work.
但是，虽然确实有一些事情是具有挑战性的
But while there are certainly things that can be challenging
关于阅读规范，甚至只是阅读这几个片段，
about reading the specification, even just reading these couple of snippets,
这个布尔列表中的这五个项目，
these five items in this bool list,
有一个非常简单的算法来确定要做什么。
there's a very straightforward algorithm for determining what to do.
现在算法背后的原因是一个完全不同的话题。
Now the reasons behind the algorithm are an entirely different topic.
它是否与其他算法一致是一个完全独立的话题。
And whether it's consistent with other algorithms is a totally separate topic.
但如果我们想了解+运算符在做什么，
But if we wanna understand what the ++ operator is doing,
预测它并避免问题。
predict it and avoid problems.
唯一的办法就是了解它会做什么。
The only way to do that is to understand what it's gonna do.
除了了解它的算法之外，我不知道有任何其他方法可以做到这一点。
And I don't know of any other way of doing that than understanding its algorithm.
所以从某种意义上说，整个课程都是为了帮助你理解
So in a sense, this whole course is really trying to help you to understand
算法，JavaScript的DNA。
the algorithms, the DNA of JavaScript.
我为什么要这么做？
Why would I wanna do that?
这是因为我希望你作为一个开发者更有效率。
It's because I want you to be more effective as a developer.
我认为对我们的效率造成最大障碍的原因之一
I think one of the things that creates the biggest roadblock to our effectiveness
作为开发人员，我们在不真正知道自己在做什么的情况下进行编码
as developers is that we code without really knowing what we're doing and
然后我们希望我们不会因此而遇到bug。
then we hope that we don't run into a bug as a result.
这对我来说很有趣，我问过这个问题
It's interesting to me, I've ask this question and
我只得到了一个有意义的答案。
I've only ever gotten one answer that made any sense.
你能说出一个你本质上是专业猜测者的职业吗？
Can you name any profession where essentially you're a professional guesser?
JavaScript开发人员和实际上在很多意义上的开发人员，但是
The JavaScript developers and in fact developers on a lot of senses but
尤其是JavaScript开发人员，我们不是真的不知道
especially JavaScript developers, isn't it true that we don't really know
为什么代码可以工作，它现在看起来就是在工作。
why the code's working, it just seems to be working right now.
目前它符合我们人工构建的任何心理模型。
And it at the moment fits whatever mental model we have artificially constructed.
就像我构造的X等于X加1，顺便说一下，这是合理的。
Like I constructed the X equals X plus one, which is reasonable by the way.
我并不是说如果那是你的思维模式你这么想很奇怪，
I'm not suggesting if that's your mental model that you're weird for thinking that,
这是合理的，但我们人为地构建了这些心理模型，并且
it's reasonable, but we artificially construct these mental models, and
它似乎起作用了，所以我们说，我希望测试套件通过。
it seems to work, and so we say, I hope the test suite passes.
你能想象这座建筑的建筑师会说，我希望墙壁不会倒塌，
Can you imagine an architect of this building saying, I hope the walls stay up,
我希望屋顶一直开着？
and I hope the roof stays on?
让我们把人放进去看看它是如何工作的。
Let's put people in it and see how it works.
让我们运行测试，看看它是如何工作的。
Let's run the tests and see how it works.
我不知道有什么其他方法可以让你对你的代码产生信心。
I don't know of any other way of developing a confidence over your code.
但这就是我努力的方向，能够理解代码在做什么。
But it's what I'm striving towards, to be able to understand what the code is doing.
就在这里，在这个特定的规范中，它确切地告诉我们发生了什么。
And right here in this particular spec, it tells us exactly what happens.
它获取旧值并对其进行两个数字运算。
It grabs the old value and does the two number operation on it.
它把它从任何东西变成一个数字。
It turns it from whatever it is into a number.
我们将讨论这两个被称为抽象运算的数字。
And we're gonna talk about that two number that's called an abstract operation.
我们会在这门课上讲到这一点。
We're gonna get into that in this course.
但我希望你能有足够的舒适感，
But I want you to be able to be comfortable enough that,
如果你不明白什么，你可以查看MDN。
if you didn't understand something, you could check MDN.
但是你猜怎么着？
But guess what?
MDN并不总是[笑]对的。
MDN is not always [LAUGH] right.
我定期修复MDN上的问题。
I fixed problems on MDN on a regular basis.
所以如果你看到的东西和你读到的不匹配，
So if there's something that you're seeing that's not matching what you're reading,
真的只有一个地方可以去，那就是规格。
there's really only one place to go and it's the spec.
如果我试图将该规范转换为某种
If I were to try to translate that specification into some kind of
我们也许可以更好地理解的JavaScript代码，基本上是这样的，
JavaScript code that we could maybe better understand, it's basically this,
+就像一个函数。
that the ++ is like a function.
它是一个运算符，但它就像一个接受原始X的函数。
It's an operator, but it's like a function that takes the original X.
就在第4行，它将其强制为一个数字。
And right there on line 4, it coerces it to a number.
并在更新后返回原始编号
And it returns that original number after having updated it
以1为增量。
with the increment of one.
所以这是一个更清晰的心智模型的例子，
So this is an illustration of having a more clear mental model,
而我得到这些的唯一途径就是把这个读回来。
and the only way that I got that was reading this back.
我看到了一些我预期会发生的事情。
I saw something that I expected to have happen.
它没有发生，而且
It didn't happen, and
我注意到这是我缺乏理解，我有错误的心理模型。
I noticed that's my lack of understanding, I have the wrong mental model.
有一种方法可以解决这个问题，阅读说明书。
And there's one way to solve that, read the spec.
每当你的大脑想法和现实之间有分歧的时候
Whenever there is a divergence between what your brain thinks and what is
实际上发生在计算机中，这就是臭虫进入代码的地方。
actually happening in the computer, that's where bugs enter the code.
这就是我真正想要的，让你感到沮丧的事情
And that's really what I'm getting at, the thing that causes you to be frustrated as
开发人员是以意想不到的方式发生错误的，我认为其中之一
a developer is that bugs happen in unexpected ways and I think one of
虫子最常见的进入方式是我们有错误的思维，
the most common ways that bugs enter is we have the incorrect thinking,
不正确的心理模型。
the incorrect mental model.
我们在想一些事情，但这与我们所想的是不同的
We're thinking something but then it's a divergent to what we're thinking and
当漏洞进入代码时，计算机正在做什么。
what the computer's doing and that's when the bug enters the code.
我的意思是，是的，有错误发生，因为你只是
I mean yes, there are bugs that happen because you just
不小心键入了两个而不是三个。
accidentally type two instead of three.
这是常有的事。
That happens.
我并不是说所有的bug都是这样的，但我认为优势集
I'm not suggesting that all bugs are this way, but I think that the predominant set
是因为我们在想一件事
of bugs that occur is because we're thinking one thing and
还有别的事情正在发生。
something else is actually happening.
你在这门课上会听到很多东西，
You're gonna hear a lot throughout this course,
但这是其中一句我会经常重复的话，而且
but this is one of those sayings that I will repeat on a regular basis, and
人们喜欢将这些称为getify的法律。
people like to refer to these as getify's laws.
所以我就开始给它们编号。
So I went ahead and just started numbering them.
这就是getify的第17条定律，当你的大脑出现分歧时
So this is getify's law number 17, when there's a divergence between your brain
而电脑就是虫子输入代码的地方。
and the computer that's where the bug enters the code.